foxy-singles.com 2013-11-26

# 

## Privacy Policy

Red Willow is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, organization whose mission is to build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the Web site www.Foxy-Singles.com. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Privacy at privacy@foxy-singles.com. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint&url= TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

### Foxy Singles Privacy Policy

**Effective May 4, 2011**

Thank you for visiting Foxy-Singles.com (the "Site"). The Site is an Internet property of Red Willow Media Inc. and its affiliated companies ("Red Willow", "we" or "us"). This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") outlines the privacy practices associated with the Site. You agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, when you: (a) access or use the Site; (b) agree to receive e-mail from us via the Site, or any other means; and/or (c) register on the Site to receive information from third party service providers ("Third Party Providers"). Personally Identifiable Information Collected. We facilitate the collection of your personally identifiable information on behalf and for the benefit of a third party when you sign up to receive products and/or services at the Site. We will not facilitate the collection of your personally identifiable information if you do not complete the applicable registration process in full. We will store your personal information if you choose sign up to use our blog on the site. The types of personally identifiable information that we collect at the Site may include, without limitation, your: (a) name; (b) e-mail address; c) date of birth; d) gender; and (e) any and all other information requested on the applicable registration form. Should you need to update/remove any of the personally identifiable information that you have submitted through the Site, you will need to contact the applicable Third Party Provider directly. Use of Personally Identifiable Information By submitting your personal information on the Site, you agree that we may share and forward such personal information with Third Party Providers in order to complete your request for specific products and/or services that you applied for at the Site ("Featured Products") from such Third Party Providers, and that they may use such personal information for any lawful purposes, subject to any restrictions contained herein. Any information that you supply through the Site to any Third Party Providers shall be governed by the applicable Third Party Providers' privacy policy. Please be advised that Red Willow is facilitating the process of gathering information and any information that you provide on the Site is forwarded to the applicable Third Party Provider.. The ultimate terms and conditions of any Featured Products provided by any Third Party Providers will be determined by those Third Party Providers. We do collect personal information such as name and email address in order to post to our blog. If you wish to change or update this personal information please email the site at privacy@foxy-singles.com Legal Disclaimer 

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you when you visit many of the pages of the Site. This non-personally identifiable information includes, without limitation, the type of browser that you use (e.g., Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome), your IP address, the type of operating system that you use (e.g., Windows or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider. We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of the Site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze Site usage, as well as to offer you products and services. We also reserve the right to use aggregate or group data about our visitors for any and all lawful purposes. Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage and/or characteristics of our visitors as a group. By visiting and/or supplying your personal information at the Site, you agree to allow us to provide such aggregate data to third parties. 

### Blogs, Forums and Chartrooms

If you use our blog on this Web site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. 

### Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

### Cookies

When an end-user visits the Site, we send a cookie and/or gif file ("Cookie") to assign an anonymous, unique identifier to the applicable end-user's Internet browser. A Cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing non-personally identifiable information about you. Cookies have many benefits to enhance your experience at the Site. To disable and reject certain Cookies, follow the instructions associated with your Internet browser. Even in the case where a user rejects a Cookie, he or she may still use this Site. Red Willow reserves the right to retain Cookie data indefinitely. We use a third-party tracking service that uses cookies and web beacons to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors and site visitation to our site in the aggregate. 

### Third Party Links

The Website may contain links to other third-party owned and/or operated websites and, where you request information from Third Party Providers, Red Willow may transfer you directly to the websites of such Third Party Providers. Red Willow is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. In some cases, you may be required to provide certain information to register or complete a transaction at such website. These third-party websites have separate privacy and data collection practices and Red Willow has no responsibility or liability relating to them. We do not endorse, nor are we responsible for the accuracy of, the privacy policies and/or terms and conditions of such website. These third party entities are independent third parties and are not affiliated with us. 

### Third-Party Offers

Red Willow provides its users with the opportunity to receive special offers, products and/or services from third parties. Where you indicate the desire to receive certain offers, products or services from a third party during the applicable information collection process, your personally identifiable information that was provided during that Red Willow information collection process will be shared with the applicable third party so that such third party may provide their product or service to you and so that you do not have to complete another information collection form to purchase or receive that product or service. Red Willow does not store any personally identifiable information that you submit in order to receive such offers from third parties. 

### Opt-Out/Unsubscribe

When you submit personally identifiable information through the Site, you have opted-in to receive information and marketing communications from the Third Party Provider. When contacted by any of these companies or third parties, you should notify them directly of your choices regarding the use of your information. To opt-out of having future third party marketing communications sent to you, you will be required to unsubscribe with the applicable third parties. 

### Minors

We do not knowingly collect information from minors under eighteen (18) years of age. No information should be submitted through the Site by individuals under eighteen (18) years of age. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children. 

### Masking

Red Willow has created the Site to facilitate the collection of information on behalf and for the benefit of a Third Party Provider. The personally identifiable information that you enter on the Site is collected by Red Willow and transferred directly to the Third Party Provider. Any information collected on the Site is the property of and will be owned by the Third Party Provider. If you do not wish to have your personally identifiable information shared with the Third Party Provider, you should not submit any information that you have entered on the Site. This Privacy Policy applies only to this Site and may differ from the privacy policy of the Third Party Provider. It is your responsibility to review the privacy policy of the Third Party Provider should you decide to continue using or opt-out of using their products and/or services. 

### Changes to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to change, modify, add and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice to you. Notice regarding any Privacy Policy changes will be placed in a prominent location on the Site and will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Site. Please check the Site periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any and all changes. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this statement, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please CONTACT US

RedWillow Media Inc.  
302-1221 Broad St  
Victoria, BC, V8W 2A4  
Canada
